

CONTACT ME AT

- Roorkee
- <u>amanneeeraj@gmail.com</u>
- in @amanguptarke
- +91 8881110843

SKILLS SUMMARY

- ••• Figma
- •••• Product Thinking
- ••• Documentations of Designs
- •••• Visual Design
- • • Design Systems
- ••• UX-Research
- •••• Mixpanel
- •••• Product Management

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- JEE ADV Rank: 14408
- RGIPT Merit Scholarship
- President at E-CELL, RGIPT
- Best Overall Co-ordinator at Techfest URJOTSAV
- Overall Batch Rank 7

AMAN GUPTA

I am a product designer based in India who loves designing efficient and beautiful experiences for complex digital products. I am a generalist with experience in a lot of different domains. Also, I got the superpower of making friends, even the introverted ones.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Postman - Product Design Intern

June 2022- Sept 2022

- Helped the company to save money that was spent on 6 Million new server call logs on the weekly cadence.
- Improved the Postman mock server creation flow, had also improved discoverability of mock server's call logs and config settings.
- Improved the experience of simulating different responses on the Postman mock server.

Tickertape(Smallcase)- Product Design Intern

Nov 2021- April 2022

- Worked on the Ecosystem of the product, and improved the discoverability of features and assets.
- Helped leads to scale the design process within organisation by helping them with better file structures and arrangements.
- Worked on several new features they are going to launch.

Cashbook(YC W21)- UX Researcher Intern

May 2021- Aug 2021

- Helped the company to scale from 500K+ downloads to 1Mil+ downloads in just 3 months.
- Improvising Micro-Interactions, conducting User Research, Persona Building, and mapping user journeys, and built a pricing model.
- Improvised usage funnels of the "Shared Book" feature of the app from 40% to 61%.

Unschool(YC W21)- Regional Head of Marketing Intern

Sept 2020 - November 2020

- Built a community of 500 students and 50 marketers.
- Generated traction of more than INR 40K+ single-handedly in a single month.

Droog- Co-Founder

Mar 2020 - Sept 2020

- Were in Y Combinator W21 top 10% of startups of all the startups participated in YC W21.
- Designed complete product and collaborated with developers
- Successfully onboarded 800 users and 200 active users within a week.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

RAJIV GANDHI INSTITUTE OF PETROLEUM TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Technology - Chemical Engineering | 2018 - 2022

- President at E-Cell, RGIPT.
- Tutor and Mentor at GYANARPAN (Govt. of India).